culturalcare.com 2017-12-18

# Privacy policy | Cultural Care Au Pair

Welcome to the culturalcare.com website (the “Website”). The terms “we”, “us”, “our”, “EF”, “Cultural Care Au Pair”, and “Cultural Care” refers to Cultural Care, Inc. and our affiliates. The term “you” refers to the customer visiting the website and/or contributing content on this website. Cultural Care Au Pair is committed to protecting the privacy of our online users and to processing your personal data in compliance with applicable privacy and data protection legislation. To make this notice easy to find, it is available in the navigation bar at the bottom of culturalcareaupair.com. This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the culturalcare.com website.

**Collection of Personal Information**

On our site, you can request information, refer host families, access and submit the host family application, and access your online account. Personal information from you will be processed by Cultural Care Au Pair both within and outside the EU/EEA/Switzerland, primarily to complete your transactions and to provide efficient, customized and meaningful experiences online.  We do not sell, rent, trade, license or otherwise disclose your specific personal information or financial information to any third parties, except when necessary to service your account. When necessary or legally required, we may share that information with our corporate affiliates, government agencies, claims handlers and business partners both within and outside the EU/EEA/Switzerland.

**Information Security**

Cultural Care Au Pair maintains physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect the confidentiality and security of personally identifiable information we collect. To guard your credit card information submitted to us online, our website uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). SSL encrypts your credit card number, name and address during transmission for your protection.

**Use of “cookies”**

Cultural Care Au Pair uses a technology nicknamed “cookies”. Cookies are pieces of information that a web site transfers to your computer’s hard disk for record keeping purposes. They tell us how and when pages on our site are visited and by how many people.

Cookies do not collect personally identifiable information, although they do identify a user’s computer. We do not combine information collected through cookies with other personally identifiable information in order to detect who you are or what your screen name or e-mail address is.

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent this. If you do so however, you may not be able to take full advantage of our web site. The complete online reservation process can for example only be accessed if you accept cookies.

As you browse our site, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in.  This enables us or our partners to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with our site. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number.  You can visit this [page ](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/)to opt out of targeted advertising.

**The Way We Use Information**

Personal information collected by Culturalcare.com is stored in secure operating environments that are not available to the public. We use the information you provide about someone else for the ‘refer a family’ program to contact that potential family about the program.  We do not share this information with outside parties. If you request our catalog or updates about our products and services, then we may also use that information to inform you of new offers, products and services which may be of interest to you. Culturalcare.com may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information. Finally, we never use or share the personally identifying information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

**Our Commitment to Children’s Privacy**

Protecting the privacy of children is especially important. For that reason, we comply in all respects with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”) and do not knowingly solicit, request or collect personal information from individuals under the age of 13.

**Reviewing or Changing Your Information**

You can access personal information online by providing your host family number or email address and password when prompted at the login. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can request changes of factual errors in your personal account from your online account, via email to your Program Director, by calling our toll-free number at 1-800-333-6056, or by sending mail to:

Cultural Care Au Pair  
One Education Street  
Cambridge, MA 02141

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**Your Consent**

By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of this information by culturalcare.com. We reserve our right not to respond to any requests to change information collected other than as indicated in “Reviewing or Changing Your Information”. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post any changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

**Tell Us What You Think**

We welcome your questions and comments about privacy. Should you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policies, please call us at 1-800-333-6056 or send us an email at [aupair@culturalcare.com ](mailto:aupair@culturalcare.com).
